# AJAY SINGH PANWAR

REACT / REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

New Delhi India

#### PHONE

+91 9599948565

#### **EMAIL**

a.panwar48656@gmail.com

#### LINKS

**LinkedIn** 

#### **SKILLS**

React Native

React

JavaScript

TypeScript

Redux

Nextjs

HTML & CSS

Android Studio

Xcode

Git

Gitlab/GitHub

#### **PROFILE**

I am a qualified and professional React/React Native Developer with 2 years of experience. Strong creative and analytical skills. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## React / React Native Developer, App Boxer Dev Private Limited

Gurgaon

Sep 2022 — Present

- Worked proficiently in React Native for cross-platform mobile app development.
- Emphasized component reusability, developing modular components to maintain code consistency.
- Utilized Redux for efficient state management and data synchronization across components.
- · Integrated Stripe SDK for secure and seamless payment processing.
- · Implemented Stripe Terminal SDK for in-person payment handling.
- · Utilized Firebase Push Notifications for real-time user engagement.
- $\cdot$  Integrated React-Native-Maps for interactive maps and geolocation features.

# React / React Native Developer, Startxlabs OPC Private Limited

Gurgaon

Jan 2022 — Aug 2022

- Contributed to React/React Native projects as a junior developer, building web and mobile applications.
- · Assisted in frontend implementation, creating visually appealing UI elements based on design specifications.
- Emphasized component reusability, developing modular components to maintain code consistency.
- Identified and fixed bugs, ensuring the stability and reliability of the applications.

# EDUCATION

# **B.Tech, Maharaja Surajmal Institute of Technology**

New Delhi

Jul 2017 — Jun 2021

CGPA: 8.78

#### 12th, Government Boys Senior Secondary School

New Delhi

Apr 2015 — Mar 2016